THE PERSONS, PLACES, ORGANIZATIONS AND EVENTS IN THE SERIES ARE FICTIONAL
시리즈에 나오는 인물, 장소, 조직 , 사건은 허구입니다.
A long time ago!
옛날에!
Let Satan ring.
사탄이 울리게 놔두세요.
Oh boys.
아 얘들아.
Hell no.
도대체 안돼.
This is your fault, asshole.
이건 네 잘못이야, 이 새끼야.
His first time.
그의 처음.
Calm down and try again.
진정하고 다시 시도해 보세요.
Aim well, you bastard.
잘 조준해라, 이 새끼야.
Kill him.
그를 죽여.
Hey.
여기요.
Hey!
여기요!
Do you miss on purpose?
일부러 놓치는 걸까요?
At the ready?
준비됐나요?
No damn.
젠장.
Damn...
젠장...
Son of a bitch.
개자식.
Killing is not easy.
죽이는 것은 쉽지 않습니다.
You need experience.
경험이 필요합니다.
THE WORST OF EVIL
최악의 악
Seungho Kwon attended Chudong Elementary School, which was closed in 1984.
권승호는 1984년 폐교된 추동초등학교를 다녔다.
Then Sanguni Middle School, which was closed in 1987.
그러다 1987년 폐교된 산구니중학교 .
So there are no alumni groups.
그래서 동창회가 없어요.
Gwangju Jeil High School
광주제일고등학교
he dropped out, so he can't be found in the student lists.
그 사람은 중퇴해서 학생 명단에서 찾을 수가 없어요.
Interesting.
흥미로운.
Nothing can be verified.
아무것도 확인할 수 없습니다.
I guess so.
그런 것 같아요.
Thank you.
감사합니다.
JANGSEOK KWON
권장석
RIKOSREKISTERI WONJU
RIKOSREKISTERI WONJU
DRUG CRIME
마약범죄
Pomo.
포모.
That woman you met, Euijeong Yu.
당신이 만난 그 여자, 유의정.
You said he was in SKPL.
그 사람이 SKPL에 있다고 했잖아요.
He's in the protection division.
그 사람은 보호 부서에 있어요.
Why would they be watching us?
왜 그들은 우리를 지켜보고 있을까요?
Well, that's what he said.
글쎄, 그가 말한 것이 바로 그것이다.
And who does he know? Seungho.
그리고 그는 누구를 알고 있나요? 승호.
What if Seungho SPIES on us in his bread?
승호가 빵 속에 우리를 염탐한다면 ?
In that case, oh damn...
그렇다면 아 젠장...
We would already be under arrest for murder.
우리는 이미 살인 혐의로 체포되었을 것입니다.
- Am I wrong? -His father is a drug addict.
- 내가 잘못? - 그의 아버지는 마약 중독자이다.
That's why they met.
그것이 그들이 만난 이유입니다.
So do you believe it?
그래서 당신은 그것을 믿습니까?
And the guys in Busan left this one. Was that a coincidence too?
그리고 부산 남자들이 이걸 남겼어요. 그것도 우연이었나?
The boss, after Seungho Kwon's arrival
사장님, 권승호 부임 후
first police officer Euijeong Yu appears, and then this.
먼저 유의정 경찰관이 등장하고, 그다음엔 이것이다.
When we were attacked, he hit the spot
우리가 공격을 받았을 때 그는 그 자리에 도착했습니다.
and took care of it.
그리고 그것을 처리했습니다.
- Isn't there anything strange about that? -Hey.
- 뭔가 이상한 점은 없나요? -여기요.
He spotted them by chance while patrolling with Yongdae.
용대와 함께 순찰을 가던 중 우연히 그들을 발견했다 .
Right, again by chance.
맞아, 또 우연히.
Don't you have too many coincidences to think about at all?
전혀 생각할 수 없을 정도로 우연의 일치가 너무 많지 않습니까 ?
Damn it. What do you want us to do?
젠장. 우리가 무엇을 하기를 원하시나요?
If one thing rots, everything rots.
한 가지가 썩으면 모든 것이 썩는다.
Isn't that our motto?
그게 우리의 모토 아닌가요?
Where are you going?
어디 가세요?
You can't go out today.
오늘은 나갈 수 없습니다.
Why not?
왜 안 돼?
What?
무엇?
What did you say?
뭐라고 하셨나요?
Nothing.
아무것도 아님.
I understand.
이해합니다.
Hey.
여기요.
Have you been drinking?
술을 마셨나요?
Why couldn't you shoot?
왜 쏘지 못하셨나요?
I am sorry.
미안해요.
Hey.
여기요.
Do not worry. You did well.
걱정 하지마. 잘했어요.
Just in case,
혹시라도,
you don't call the police
너 경찰에 전화하지 마
because of guilt or something?
죄책감 때문인가 뭔가?
Should I call the police?
경찰에 전화해야 하나요?
Well, that female police officer is a dictionary.
글쎄, 그 여자 경찰관은 사전이다.
I thought you could call him and hang out.
나는 당신 이 그에게 전화해서 놀 수 있다고 생각했습니다.
"Those bastards ordered someone to be killed."
"저 놈들은 사람을 죽이라고 명령했어요."
Stop it. I don't want to listen to that.
그만해요. 나는 그 말을 듣고 싶지 않습니다.
You think you get to choose, abscess?
선택할 수 있다고 생각하세요, 농양?
Listen.
듣다.
So that I can wear gold watches on my wrists instead of handcuffs,
손목에 수갑 대신 금시계를 차고 다닐 수 있도록 ,
I've had to use my brain all my life .
나는 평생 동안 두뇌를 사용해야 했습니다 .
You're Taeho's cousin, okay.
당신은 태호의 사촌이군요.
But you're not one of us.
하지만 당신은 우리 중 하나가 아닙니다.
What do you mean?
무슨 뜻이에요?
Why not? Because I'm not from Gangnam huh?
왜 안 돼? 왜냐면 난 강남 사람이 아니거든?
Oh boys.
아 얘들아.
Chief Seo.
서 실장님.
Command him back to patrol.
그에게 다시 순찰하라고 명령하세요.
Mr.
씨.
Hey, Seungho Kwon.
안녕하세요 권승호님.
Sir?
선생님?
I'm not from Gangnam either.
나도 강남 출신이 아니다.
If we arrest them for this,
만약 우리가 이 일로 그들을 체포한다면,
the investigation must be suspended.
수사는 중단되어야 한다.
Let's identify the victim
피해자 신원을 밝혀보자
and let's hide this for now.
지금은 이것을 숨기겠습니다.
Didn't Detective Park cause quite a stir?
박형사님이 꽤 파문을 일으키지 않았나요?
He is apparently under suspicion again.
그는 다시 의심을 받고 있는 것 같습니다.
Trust must be restored.
신뢰를 회복해야 합니다.
Just this once.
딱 한번만.
Could you help us?
우리를 도와주실 수 있나요?
With what?
무엇으로?
Commissioner Yu, you are the only police officer,
유 위원님, 당신은 유일한 경찰관이십니다.
who can meet Gicheul Jung.
정기철을 만날 수 있는 사람.
ACCUSES AGAINST JUNG
정에 대한 비난
THE MURDERS OF KYUNGCHUL JANG AND AN UNKNOWN MAN
장경철과 신원불명의 살인사건
ILLEGAL POSSESSION OF WEAPONS
무기 불법 소지
- Here is a list of companies. -Clear.
- 회사 목록은 다음과 같습니다. -분명한.
Hello?
안녕하세요?
Hi Gicheul. Euijeong here.
안녕하세요 기철님. 여기 의정이요.
I asked Seungho for your number.
승호한테 전화번호 물어봤는데
I see.
알겠어요.
Would you like to go alone?
혼자 가고 싶나요?
Who do you meet?
누구를 만나나요?
Wait here.
여기서 기다리세요.
Let's sit down.
앉자.
What the heck?
이런 젠장?
Dohyung, what's going on?
도형아, 무슨 일이야?
Why does Euijeong meet Gicheul Jung?
의정은 왜 정기철을 만나는 걸까?
Your wife will help us.
당신의 아내가 우리를 도울 것입니다.
With what?
무엇으로?
He tells Gicheul,
그는 기철에게 이렇게 말한다.
that Seungho Kwon is trustworthy and worth keeping around.
권승호는 믿을 만하고 곁에 둘 가치가 있는 사람이다.
Why should Euijeong...
왜 의정이...
This investigation is dangerous.
이번 조사는 위험해요.
Why did you bring Euijeong along?
의정은 왜 데려왔나요?
This is wrong.
이것은 잘못된 것입니다.
He agreed himself.
그는 스스로 동의했습니다.
-Dohyung. -Listen.
-도형. -듣다.
We didn't ask your wife to come along.
우리는 당신 아내에게 같이 오라고 요청하지 않았습니다.
We asked for help from SKPL's talented inspector,
SKPL의 유능한 검사관에게 도움을 요청했고 ,
From Euijeong Yu.
유의정으로부터.
Junmo, we can trust Inspector Yu.
준모 경위님은 믿을 수 있어요.
How did you know my mother was sick?
우리 엄마가 아픈 걸 어떻게 알았어?
I know a police officer.
나는 경찰관을 알고 있다.
The day we met
우리가 만난 날
was so surprising that I was rude.
너무 놀라서 무례했어요.
And you weren't.
그리고 당신은 그렇지 않았습니다.
By the way, you're even more handsome.
그건 그렇고, 당신이 더 잘생겼어요.
Ta-daa.
짜잔.
Did you keep this?
이거 보관했어?
I thought you'd like to have it sometime.
언젠가 갖고 싶다고 생각했어요 .
Euijeong.
의정.
Do you remember?
기억 나니?
Do you like it?
당신은 그것을 좋아합니까?
I like.
좋아요.
If you find something nice in the church shop,
교회 상점에서 좋은 물건을 발견했다면,
buy me too
나도 사줘
I'll buy you something better.
내가 더 좋은 걸 사줄게.
More expensive.
더 비싼.
When?
언제?
-Wait a minute. -What now?
-잠깐 기다려요. - 지금은요?
What would have happened to us?
우리에게 무슨 일이 일어났을까요?
without what happened to mom?
엄마한테 무슨 일이 있었나요?
I hope you are kind to Seungho.
승호에게 친절하길 바랍니다.
He suffered a lot as a child.
그는 어렸을 때 많은 고통을 겪었습니다.
Take good care of him.
그를 잘 돌봐주세요.
It must be hard to take care of your mother.
어머니를 돌보기가 힘들겠네요.
It does not matter.
그것은 중요하지 않습니다.
I try to fit in whenever I can.
나는 가능할 때마다 적응하려고 노력합니다.
Thanks, but you don't have to.
고마워요. 하지만 그럴 필요는 없어요.
You're busy too.
당신도 바쁩니다.
Does your husband ever visit your mother?
당신의 남편은 당신의 어머니를 방문한 적이 있습니까?
The nurse thought I was her son-in-law.
간호사는 내가 그녀의 사위라고 생각했습니다.
If she asks about your husband,
그녀가 남편에 대해 묻는다면,
just say you broke up
그냥 헤어졌다고 해
and leave it at that.
그대로 두세요.
Actually, I quit.
사실 저는 그만뒀어요.
But only part of my family knows.
하지만 우리 가족 중 일부만 알고 있어요.
I only know cops.
내가 아는 건 경찰뿐이다.
I was afraid that the information would spread and problems would follow.
정보가 퍼지고 문제가 생길까 두려웠습니다 .
I didn't even tell mom.
나는 엄마에게도 말하지 않았습니다.
Everything hurts and happens.
모든 일은 아프고 일어난다.
No worries.
걱정 마.
Did you know that Euijeong broke up?
의정이 헤어진거 아시나요?
In.
안에.
Don't tell anyone I met him.
내가 그 사람을 만났다고 아무에게도 말하지 마세요.
We have known him for a long time, so it suits us.
우리는 그를 오랫동안 알고 있었기 때문에 우리에게 적합합니다.
However, others will not like it.
그러나 다른 사람들은 그것을 좋아하지 않을 것입니다.
He's a policeman.
그는 경찰관입니다.
All right, boss.
알겠습니다, 보스.
Welcome, boss.
환영합니다, 보스.
I guess I'll see him often from now on,
앞으로는 자주 만날 것 같아요.
just so you know.
그냥 알아두세요.
All right, boss.
알겠습니다, 보스.
Patrolling is enough for now.
지금은 순찰만으로도 충분합니다.
Hello?
안녕하세요?
Hi dad.
안녕 아빠.
Clear.
분명한.
Seung Ho.
승호
Yeah, boss?
응, 보스?
Get dressed.
옷을 입다.
What now?
지금은 무엇입니까?
Euijeong's mother has passed away.
의정의 어머니가 돌아가셨습니다.
CHAPEL
예배당
Hold on, boss.
잠깐만요, 보스.
I've thought about it.
나는 그것에 대해 생각했습니다.
I think you should go alone.
내 생각에는 당신이 혼자 가야 할 것 같아요.
It looks better if you go alone
혼자 가면 더 좋을 것 같아요
to comfort Euijeong.
의정을 위로하기 위해.
I'll go pay my respects later.
나중에 가서 경의를 표하겠습니다 .
REST IN PEACE GICHEUL JUNG
편히 쉬세요 정기철
Are you okay?
괜찮으세요?
We went to the same church.
우리는 같은 교회에 다녔어요.
He knew the mother well.
그는 그 어머니를 잘 알고 있었습니다.
- This is my wife. - Day.
- 이사람은 내 와이프 야. - 낮.
Thank you for coming.
와주셔서 감사합니다.
I am sure he is resting in heaven now.
나는 그가 지금 천국에서 쉬고 있다고 확신합니다.
How did you know? I didn't inform you.
어떻게 알았나요? 나는 당신에게 알리지 않았습니다.
I told you I know the police.
내가 경찰을 안다고 말했잖아.
Seungho, thanks for coming too.
승호 씨도 와줘서 고마워요.
Of course.
물론.
Uncle.
삼촌.
Can you solve this for me?
이 문제를 해결해 주실 수 있나요?
Uncle is here.
삼촌이 여기 있어요.
Let's go figure it out.
알아내러 가자.
EUMSEONG POLICE STATION DETECTIVE JUNMO PARK
음성경찰서 형사 박준모
Gicheul, shall we go get some oxygen?
기철아, 산소 좀 마시러 갈까?
Sure.
확신하는.
It breaks my heart to see you alone.
당신이 혼자 있는 걸 보니 마음이 아프네요.
You shouldn't be lonely.
외로워서는 안 됩니다.
I'm starting to hate your ex-husband.
나는 당신의 전남편을 싫어하기 시작했습니다.
Will he appear now?
이제 그 사람이 나타나나요?
This is my husband.
이 사람은 내 남편이에요.
Here is my friend from church.
여기 교회에 다니는 내 친구가 있습니다.
I have met fellow church members at our wedding
나는 결혼식에서 교회 동료들을 만났습니다.
and in our homesickness.
그리고 우리의 향수병에.
I haven't met you before.
나는 당신을 전에 만난 적이 없습니다.
Since you immediately came to visit,
바로 방문해주셔서
you must be a very close friend.
당신은 아주 친한 친구임에 틀림없어요.
I went to see his mother in the hospital a while ago.
나는 얼마 전 그의 어머니를 병원에 만나러 갔다 .
And he told me
그리고 그는 나에게 말했다
that he likes his son-in-law more than his two sons.
그는 두 아들보다 사위를 더 좋아한다는 것이다 .
When was the last time you visited him in the hospital?
그를 마지막으로 병원에 방문한 게 언제였나요?
I know you broke up, but did it even cross your mind,
헤어진 건 알지만 그 생각이 떠올랐나요?
that he would like to see his son-in-law before he dies?
죽기 전에 사위를 만나고 싶다고 ?
Do you even have the right to mourn him?
당신에게는 그를 애도할 권리가 있습니까?
Gicheul, stop it.
기철아, 그만해.
Hey.
여기요.
We don't talk about other people's family matters,
우리는 다른 사람의 가족 문제에 대해 이야기하지 않습니다.
especially a grieving family.
특히 슬픔에 잠긴 가족.
You should stop too.
당신도 그만둬야 해요.
There will still be guests, so say goodbye and come back inside.
아직 손님이 있을 테니 작별 인사를 하고 다시 안으로 들어가세요.
I will go.
나는 갈 것이다.
Thank you for visiting.
방문해 주셔서 감사합니다.
Thanks to you too, Seungho.
승호씨도 고마워요.
I am praying for your mother.
나는 당신의 어머니를 위해 기도하고 있습니다.
If you need, call anytime.
필요하시면 언제든지 전화주세요.
I'm going to the bathroom.
나는 화장실에 갈거야.
Junmo.
준모.
Hei, Junmo!
안녕, 준모!
Why didn't you report to us?
왜 우리에게 보고하지 않았나요?
At least I have to pay my last respects to my mother-in-law.
적어도 시어머니께 마지막 경의를 표해야 합니다.
Do you want to abandon our operation?
우리 작전을 포기하시겠습니까?
I'm really sorry, Junmo.
정말 미안해, 준모.
I...
나...
I'll stay until he's buried.
나는 그가 묻힐 때까지 머물겠습니다.
Damn damn.
젠장, 젠장.
I'm really sorry.
정말 죄송해요.
Does the food taste good?
음식 맛이 좋나요?
Yes ma'am. It is delicious.
네 부인. 맛있다.
How is your work going?
일은 순조로워 요?
Very. I try my best.
매우. 나는 최선을 다합니다.
That's how it should be. Trust yourself.
그렇게되어야합니다. 자신을 믿으십시오.
- I will do that. -Do what you must...
- 나는 그렇게 할 것이다. - 해야 할 일을 해라...
-Yes. -...and what you want.
-예. -...그리고 당신이 원하는 것.
Yes ma'am.
네 부인.
Euijeong's father and brother do not tolerate,
의정의 아버지와 형은 참지 못하고,
but don't worry about it.
하지만 걱정하지 마세요.
Euijeong likes you a lot, Junmo.
의정이 준모를 많이 좋아해요.
And I like that you smile.
그리고 나는 당신이 웃는 것을 좋아합니다.
That's the most important thing, isn't it?
그게 가장 중요한 것 아닌가?
When we laugh and spend time together,
함께 웃으며 시간을 보낼 때,
we become a family.
우리는 가족이 됩니다.
That's right.
좋아요.
Thank you.
감사합니다.
Seungho, do you know how your mother is?
승호야, 네 엄마는 어떤지 알아?
Yes.
예.
She reportedly had a baby with some guy
그녀는 어떤 남자와 아이를 가졌다고 합니다
and live contentedly.
그리고 만족스럽게 살아요.
Don't you hate him when he didn't look for you?
그가 당신을 찾지 않았을 때 당신은 그를 미워하지 않습니까 ?
Do I hate him?
내가 그를 싫어합니까?
I'm not sure.
잘 모르겠습니다.
Instead of him
그 대신
I wouldn't even want to think about our family.
우리 가족에 대해서는 생각조차 하고 싶지 않아요.
Deuce.
듀스.
My father often beat my mother.
아버지는 어머니를 자주 때렸습니다.
During high school, we ran away from home with my siblings and mother.
고등학교 시절, 우리는 어머니, 형제자매들과 함께 가출을 했습니다 .
I said I'd kill dad if he looked for us.
나는 아빠가 우리를 찾으면 죽이겠다고 말했어요.
That bastard...
그 놈...
He still came, undeterred.
그는 여전히 단념하지 않고 왔습니다.
So he died.
그래서 그는 죽었습니다.
Not by me, but by my mother.
내가 아니라 어머니가.
Pomo.
포모.
I want to succeed.
나는 성공하고 싶다.
At first
처음에는
I came to work for you to get revenge for Taeho.
나는 태호의 복수를 위해 당신 밑에서 일하러 왔습니다 .
But now
그러나 지금
I want to be successful just like you.
나도 당신처럼 성공하고 싶어요.
I don't want to live as the son of a drug addict.
나는 마약 중독자의 아들로 살고 싶지 않습니다.
Do you understand?
이해했나요?
In Gangnam.
강남에서.
The man who succeeded in Gangnam,
강남에서 성공한 남자,
Seungho Kwon.
권승호.
I want to be him.
나는 그 사람이 되고 싶다.
I will help you.
내가 당신을 도울 것입니다.
Help me, boss.
도와주세요, 보스.
But I want a return favor.
하지만 나는 보답을 원해요.
I'll do anything.
나는 무엇이든 할 것이다.
What do you want?
당신은 무엇을 원합니까?
I want the me and Euijeong thing to work.
나와 의정이 잘 됐으면 좋겠다.
I need your help with that.
그러려면 당신의 도움이 필요해요.
And your support.
그리고 당신의 지원.
Alright. I'll do it.
괜찮은. 나는 그것을 할 거 야.
I will help you.
내가 당신을 도울 것입니다.
Pomo.
포모.
I am
그래요
sailed the Pacific for a year at a time.
1년 동안 태평양을 항해했습니다 .
Now I'm starting to feel queasy.
이제 나는 메스꺼움을 느끼기 시작했습니다.
I miss the smell of the sea.
바다 냄새가 그리워요.
The next time you go fishing,
다음번에 낚시하러 갈 때,
could i come along?
나도 같이 가도 될까?
Just like in that picture.
저 그림처럼 말이죠.
I would like to go on a fishing trip with you.
나는 당신과 함께 낚시 여행을 가고 싶습니다.
It is the hobby of our three leaders.
우리 세 리더의 취미입니다.
And you would like to join already?
이미 가입하고 싶으신가요?
Why not?
왜 안 돼?
No...
아니요...
Didn't Euijeong ask to take care of me?
의정이가 나 좀 챙겨달라고 하지 않았어 ?
Let me come along.
나도 따라가자.
Wait and see.
기다려 보세요.
All right, boss.
알겠습니다, 보스.
Thank you.
감사합니다.
Pomo.
포모.
I'll do my best.
난 최선을 다 할거야.
Call, press one.
전화하세요. 하나를 누르세요.
Leave a message,
메시지를 남겨주세요,
press two.
2개를 누르세요.
Please leave a message.
메시지를 남겨주세요.
Hey, Euijeong.
안녕, 의정.
Me here.
나 여기 있어요.
I'm really sorry.
정말 죄송해요.
Sorry I couldn't visit your mom.
미안해, 네 엄마를 방문할 수 없었어.
I just...
난 그냥...
Sorry to cause this mess.
이런 혼란을 야기해서 죄송합니다.
Sorry I was so stupid.
미안 내가 너무 멍청했어.
And...
그리고...
I just...
난 그냥...
Sorry I'm not good enough.
죄송합니다. 저는 실력이 부족합니다.
Sorry for everything.
모든 죄송합니다.
Sorry.
죄송합니다.
Euijeong.
의정.
I love you.
사랑해요.
Does anyone have a fire?
불난 사람 있나요?
No thanks.
고맙지 만 사양 할게.
Hard, huh?
힘들죠?
Always have to follow the boss's schedule,
항상 상사의 일정을 따라야 하고,
and at night there is no place of your own to stay.
밤에는 너희가 머물 곳이 없느니라 .
It does not matter.
그것은 중요하지 않습니다.
Do not worry.
걱정 하지마.
Around next spring
내년 봄쯤
the boss will probably give you your own place.
상사가 아마 당신에게 자리를 줄 것입니다.
Thank you.
감사합니다.
You look cute when you smile.
웃는 모습이 귀엽네요.
- Seungho. -So?
- 승호. -그래서?
I'm younger than you.
나는 당신보다 어리다.
Do you mind if I speak casually?
제가 아무렇지도 않게 얘기해도 될까요?
None.
없음.
Really?
정말?
What did you and the boss do yesterday?
당신과 상사는 어제 무엇을 했나요?
Where did you go?
어디로 갔나요?
Didn't he tell?
그가 말하지 않았나요?
Told.
말했다.
What he said?
그가 뭐라고 말했나요?
Should I tell you
말해야 하나?
what did the boss say to me?
사장님이 나한테 뭐라고 했어?
He told it all, so you can tell it.
그는 모든 것을 말했으므로 당신은 그것을 말할 수 있습니다.
We visited Taeho's urn vault.
태호의 항아리 금고를 방문했습니다.
Why is it such a big secret?
왜 그렇게 큰 비밀이 있는 걸까요?
Tell me about all such things. Is it clear?
그런 것들 에 대해 모두 말해주세요 . 명백합니까?
Thank you.
감사합니다.
When you were driving that night.
그날 밤에 운전을 했을 때요.
I hope we will continue to get along.
우리가 계속해서 잘 지내길 바랍니다.
Choose your leaders wisely.
지도자를 현명하게 선택하십시오.
I believe I will.
나는 그럴 것이라고 믿습니다.
Neither of us are from Gangnam.
우리 둘 다 강남 출신이 아니다.
The higher ups seemed to have a way of making big bucks.
상류층은 큰돈을 벌 수 있는 방법이 있는 것 같았습니다.
We should figure it out soon too.
우리도 빨리 알아내야 해요.
True, sir.
그렇습니다.
JAEGEON LOGISTICS
대전물류
I was going to tip over.
나는 넘어질 예정이었다.
-Sorry. - Focus.
-죄송합니다. - 집중하다.
Corotan.
코로탄.
Are you paying? You have hand cards.
당신은 지불하고 있습니까? 당신은 핸드 카드를 가지고 있습니다.
I'll pay and see.
결제하고 볼게요.
Who are you?
누구세요?
Who the hell are you?
도대체 당신은 누구 요?
Is that Geon Kang from Busan?
저 사람 부산 출신 강건이요?
Hi Geo. Did you come alone?
안녕하세요 지오입니다. 혼자 오셨나요?
What brings you here?
여기에서 당신을 제공합니다?
Let's start a war, together.
함께 전쟁을 시작합시다.
Am I there?
내가 거기 있나요?
I've never seen this bastard before.
나는 이런 놈을 본 적이 없습니다.
What?
무엇?
The picture has probably been edited.
아마도 사진이 편집된 것 같습니다.
Who the hell did this?
도대체 누가 이런 짓을 한 걸까요?
What kind of fool would dare to do that?
어떤 바보가 감히 그런 짓을 하겠나?
Gicheul Jung Gangnam Unionist.
정기철 강남연합회.
Help me,
도와주세요,
then you get Nonhyeon-dong and Yeoksam-dong.
그러면 논현동 과 역삼동이 나옵니다.
Fine.
괜찮은.
What the hell?
대체 뭐야?
I'm sure you know me.
나는 당신이 나를 알고 있다고 확신합니다.
We need to talk.
우리는 이야기를 해야 합니다.
-Damn... -Wait.
- 젠장... - 잠깐만요.
I haven't finished yet.
아직 끝나지 않았어요.
Have you eaten yet?
아직 식사하셨나요?
When playing billiards, Chinese food is a must.
당구를 치려면 중국 음식이 필수입니다.
I can offer.
나는 제안할 수 있다.
- How much? -18,000 won.
- 얼마나 많이? -18,000원.
- 18 thousand? -So.
- 18,000? -그래서.
Wait.
기다리다.
You're in Gangnam Union right?
강남유니온 맞죠?
What do you want?
당신은 무엇을 원합니까?
Nice to meet you.
만나서 반가워요.
When there are no parents in the organization,
조직에 부모가 없을 때,
but all are the same age,
그런데 나이는 다 똑같아.
there will certainly be a lot of disagreement.
분명 이견이 많을 것이다.
Because you are so successful,
당신이 너무 성공했기 때문에,
my boss wants to talk to you.
내 상사가 당신과 얘기하고 싶어해요.
You'll be fine, young man.
괜찮을 거예요, 젊은이.
Nice bar.
좋은 바.
How long do you think you can maintain your rich lifestyle?
귀하는 언제까지 풍요로운 생활방식을 유지할 수 있다고 생각하십니까 ?
Imagine yourself two, three
둘, 셋을 상상해 보세요
or ten years from now.
아니면 지금으로부터 10년 후.
Nothing has changed.
아무것도 변하지 않았다.
You still bow down to your own age
아직도 네 나이에 굴복하는구나
and you are looked down upon.
그리고 당신은 무시당합니다.
This whole gang is abnormal.
이 갱단 전체가 비정상이에요.
It depends on one man, Gicheul Jung,
정기철 한 사람에게 달려 있다 .
and his charisma.
그리고 그의 카리스마.
What do you do if he gets stabbed to death?
그 사람이 칼에 찔려 죽으면 어떻게 합니까?
Our gang controls 50% of Seoul,
우리 갱단은 서울의 50%를 장악하고 있고,
and we are ready to take you along.
우리는 당신을 데려갈 준비가 되어 있습니다.
Our organization is nationwide and growing rapidly.
우리 조직은 전국적으로 성장하고 있으며 빠르게 성장하고 있습니다.
You are not the only one,
당신은 유일한 사람이 아닙니다.
which we are trying to recruit.
우리가 모집하려고 하는 사람입니다.
If you refuse, someone else will accept our Offer.
귀하가 거절하면 다른 사람이 우리의 제안을 수락하게 됩니다.
Consider carefully.
신중하게 고려하십시오.
For now, we just want to
지금으로서는 단지
that you are observing what Gicheul Jung is doing.
정기철이 하는 일을 관찰하고 있다는 것.
Where does he go and with whom.
그는 누구와 어디로 가는가?
We want to know it in real time.
우리는 그것을 실시간으로 알고 싶습니다.
- I'm pissed. -Hey.
- 화났어. -여기요.
Gicheul, I need to get to the hospital right now.
기철아, 나 지금 당장 병원에 가야 해.
Hyeok was forced into action.
혁은 어쩔 수 없이 행동에 나섰다.
I hear bleeding from the vagina.
질에서 피가 나는 소리가 들립니다.
What if the baby is in danger?
아기가 위험에 처하면 어떻게 되나요?
What do you mean?
무슨 뜻이에요?
I don't think I'll be able to go fishing tomorrow. Go without me.
내일은 낚시하러 갈 수 없을 것 같아요. 나 없이 가세요.
-Hey... -I'm sorry.
-안녕... -미안해요.
Wait.
기다리다.
Keep us updated.
계속해서 업데이트해 주세요.
Oh shit.
아 젠장.
Boss, I don't think we can do it alone.
보스, 우리 혼자서는 할 수 없을 것 같아요.
We need someone to keep watch at the port.
항구를 감시할 사람이 필요해요 .
Let's take one of the men with us.
남자 한 명을 데려가자.
- We don't say what we do. -Alright.
- 우리는 우리가 무엇을 하는지 말하지 않습니다. -괜찮은.
- He can wait at the port. -Clear.
- 그는 항구에서 기다릴 수 있어요. -분명한.
I ask Chief Seo to get ready.
서 실장에게 준비를 부탁한다.
Seunghoa.
승호.
Don't bother, boss.
방해하지 마세요, 보스.
I said we won't tell him.
나는 그에게 말하지 않겠다고 말했다.
It's way too early.
너무 이르다.
Jungbae.
정배.
Yeah, boss.
응, 보스.
If we include Seungho,
승호까지 포함하면
we will find out
우리는 알아낼 것이다
is he in touch with the driver.
그 사람이 운전사와 연락을 하고 있나요?
All right, boss.
알겠습니다, 보스.
Seung Ho.
승호
-Mr? -Have you washed?
-씨? -씻었어요?
I am.
그래요.
Don't drink today. Go to bed early.
오늘은 술을 마시지 마세요. 일찍 잠자리에.
Is there something going on?
무슨 일이라도 있는 걸까요?
You're asking too much again.
또 너무 많은 걸 요구하시네요.
We're going fishing, so be ready.
우리는 낚시하러 갈 테니 준비하세요.
I understand.
이해합니다.
May I ask why we changed cars?
우리가 왜 차를 바꿨는지 물어봐도 될까요?
Are we making sure we are not tracked?
우리가 추적되지 않도록 하고 있나요?
Can you even fish in the middle of the night?
한밤중에도 낚시를 할 수 있나요?
-Hello? -Hello, boss.
-안녕하세요? -안녕하세요, 사장님.
Flat tire, I'm stuck here.
타이어 펑크, 여기 갇혔어요.
Sorry.
죄송합니다.
That slip almost killed me.
그 실수로 거의 죽을 뻔했어요.
I'm calling for help.
도움을 요청하고 있어요.
Could you go ahead?
계속 해주시겠어요?
Alright.
괜찮은.
What the hell?
대체 뭐야?
Let them go ahead.
계속하도록 놔두세요.
Oh shit.
아 젠장.
-Stick to the board! -Damn it.
-보드에 붙어라! -젠장.
Damn it!
젠장!
That big head!
그 큰 머리!
Satan!
사탄!
Are you okay?
괜찮으세요?
What the hell is this?
이게 대체 뭐야?
Work now.
지금 일하세요.
Movement!
움직임!
There!
거기!
Help!
돕다!
You assholes!
이 멍청아!
Son of a bitch!
개자식!
Let go!
가자!
Catch them!
그들을 잡아!
Speed ​​up!
속도를 올리다!
God!
하나님!
Short!
짧은!
Translation: Mikko Piekkala
번역: Mikko Piekkala